{"qid": "0", "question": "Could you tell me who are the authors of \"sts observations of landau levels at graphite surfaces?\"", "answer": "Yasuhiro Niimi, Hiroshi Kambara, Masaru Tsukada, Katsunori Tagami, Hiroshi Fukuyama, T. Matsui"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Could you tell me who are the authors of \"formation of single quantum dot in single walled carbon nanotube channel using focused ion beam technique?\"", "answer": "Koichi Inoue, Hirokazu Ozaki, Kenzo Maehashi, Shu Seki, Kazuhiko Matsumoto, Seiichi Tagawa, Yasuhide Ohno"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Could you tell me who are the authors of \"high sensitivity nanometer scale infrared spectroscopy using a contact mode microcantilever with an internal resonator paddle?\"", "answer": "William P. King, Debra Cook, Jonathan R. Felts, Craig Prater, Kevin Kjoller"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"unraveling doping capability of conjugated polymers for strategic manipulation of electric dipole layer toward efficient charge collection in perovskite solar cells?\"", "answer": "Hyungtak Seo, Jongmin Lee, So Jeong Shin, Sang Eun Yoon, Jong H. Kim, Jaehong Park, Bong-Gi Kim, Dong Ryeol Whang, Hui Joon Park, Ji Min Han, Sang Yeon Lee"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"isomerization of azobenzene and the enhancement of dynamic heterogeneities in molecular glass formers?\" ", "answer": "Michael Chrysos, J.-B. Accary, Victor Teboul"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"ni2p grown in situ on milled black phosphorus flakes and its high energy storage performance?\" ", "answer": "Wanying Liu, Yabo Zhu, Xinxi Zhang, Qian Xu, Xiaokuan Ban, Yuting Cui"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"promotion of sers and catalytic activities with bimetallic and ternary concave nanolayers?\"", "answer": "Chih Chia Huang, I-Wen Sun, Wei-Shan Huang"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper titled \"tensile properties of high strength polyacrylonitrile pan based and high modulus pitch based hybrid carbon fibers reinforced epoxy matrix composite?\"", "answer": "Jenn-Ming Yang, Yutaka Kagawa, Kimiyoshi Naito"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper titled \"hydration of mgo 100 surface promoted at 011 steps?\"", "answer": "Tatsuya Murakami, Masahiko Tomitori, Akira Sasahara"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"microstructure and growth model for rice hull derived sic whiskers?\"", "answer": "Steven Nutt"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "Where is the paper \"sintering the role of interface energies\" published?", "answer": "applied surface science"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "Where is the paper \"interlayer catalytic exfoliation realizing scalable production of large size pristine few layer graphene\" published?", "answer": "scientific reports"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "What is the publishing venue of the paper \"high temperature creep in a 2 3 4 garnet ca3ga2ge3o12\"?", "answer": "journal of materials science"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "Can you tell me where the paper \"a systematic analysis of transformation stress anisotropy in shape memory alloys\" was published?", "answer": "philosophical magazine"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "Can you tell me where the paper \"a ferroelectric electrochemical modulated organic synapse for ultraflexible artificial visual perception system\" was published?", "answer": "advanced materials"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "Can you tell me where the paper \"performance of p type silicon oxide windows in amorphous silicon solar cell\" was published?", "answer": "solar energy materials and solar cells"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "In which publication was the paper \"internal friction behaviour during martensitic transformation in shape memory alloys processed by powder metallurgy\" released?", "answer": "materials science and engineering a structural materials properties microstructure and processing"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "Can you tell me where the paper \"optical absorption spectrum oscillator strengths magnetic splitting factors and paramagnetic susceptibility of nd3 doped into liyo2\" was published?", "answer": "journal of alloys and compounds"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "What is the publishing venue of the paper \"a novel crack healing technique in a low carbon steel by cyclic phase transformation heat treatment the process and mechanism\"?", "answer": "materials science and engineering a structural materials properties microstructure and processing"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "In which publication was the paper \"synthesis of a multifunctional bisphosphate and its flame retardant application in epoxy resin\" released?", "answer": "polymer degradation and stability"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Who collaborates with author N. S. Vasile to write paper \"numerical study of the effect of channel aspect ratio on particle focusing in acoustophoretic devices\"?", "answer": "Giancarlo Canavese, L. Spigarelli, Candido Pirri"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "Who partnered with author Calvin D. Quilty to author the paper \"reversible epitaxial electrodeposition of metals in battery anodes\"?", "answer": "David C. Bock, Esther S. Takeuchi, Duhan Zhang, Lei Wang, Jingxu Zheng, Cherno Jaye, Qing Zhao, Tian Tang, Xiaotun Liu, Amy C. Marschilok, Jiefu Yin, Genesis D. Renderos, Lynden A. Archer, Yue Deng, Kenneth J. Takeuchi"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "Who teamed up with author Wenjin Yue to write the paper \"from binary to multicomponent photoactive layer a promising complementary strategy to efficient hybrid solar cells\"?", "answer": "Weili Meng, Zeliang Qiu, Feng Li, Qiquan Qiao, Fapei Zhang, Changwen Liu, Mingtai Wang"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "Who partnered with author Sohail Murad to author the paper \"thermal transport through a fluid solid interface\"?", "answer": "Ishwar K. Puri"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "Who partnered with author Takashi Nakajima to author the paper \"domain switching kinetics in vinylidene fluoride tetrafluoroethylene copolymer thin films\"?", "answer": "Alexei Gruverman, Yuuta Nakagawa, Yoichiro Hashizume, Soichiro Okamura"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Who joined forces with author A. Deruyttere to pen down \"fatigue softening of severely cold drawn low carbon steel\"?", "answer": "Lucas Delaey, Zou Hua Min"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Who joined forces with author R. M. Lum to pen down \"improvements in the modulation amplitude of submicron gratings produced in n inp by direct photoelectrochemical etching\"?", "answer": "Paul A. Kohl, Frederick W. Ostermayer, A. A. Ballman, Alastair M. Glass"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Who collaborates with author Amit Salvi to write paper \"specimen size effects in the off axis compression test of unidirectional carbon fiber tow composites\"?", "answer": "Anthony M. Waas, Ari Garo Caliskan"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Who worked alongside author Yasuhisa Ando for the composition of \"development of a microlateral force sensor and its evaluation using lateral force microscopy\"?", "answer": "Naoki Shiraishi"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Who collaborates with author Gong Li to write paper \"effects of pre introduced shear origin zones on mechanical property of zrcu metallic glass\"?", "answer": "Riping Liu, L. Qi, Shidong Feng, W. Zhao"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Who are the authors of both the papers \"thermal transport and storage performances of nacl kcl naf eutectic salt for high temperatures latent heat\" and \"effects of proton irradiation on upright metamorphic gainp gainas ge triple junction solar cells\"?", "answer": "Zhong Li"}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Who are the authors of both the papers \"dynamic covalent formation of concave disulfide macrocycles mechanically interlocked with single walled carbon nanotubes\" and \"adsorption behavior of a cyano functionalized porphyrin on cu 111 and ag 111 from molecular wires to ordered supramolecular two dimensional aggregates\"?", "answer": "Bernd Meyer"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"integrated plasma synthesis of efficient catalytic nanostructures for fuel cell electrodes\" and paper \"a high sensitivity momentum flux measuring instrument for plasma thruster exhausts and diffusive plasmas\"?", "answer": "Christine Charles"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Who is the writer of both \"understanding fractional order surface plasmons\" and \"optically tuned terahertz modulator based on annealed multilayer mos2\" papers?", "answer": "Yuping Yang"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Who is the writer of both \"epoxy composites using functionalized alumina platelets as reinforcements\" and \"dynamic fracture of a functionally gradient material having discrete property variation\" papers?", "answer": "Venkitanarayanan Parameswaran"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Who are the authors of both the papers \"reactively sputtered zn o s buffer layers for controlling band alignment of cu in ga se2 thin film solar cell interface\" and \"ultrafast wavelength dependent carrier dynamics related to metastable defects in cu in ga se2 solar cells with chemically deposited zn o s buffer layer\"?", "answer": "Myeong Eon Kim"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Who are the authors of both the papers \"impact of electron beam heating during 3d nanoprinting\" and \"different shades of oxide from nanoscale wetting mechanisms to contact printing of gallium based liquid metals\"?", "answer": "Eva Mutunga"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"nanoformulation and encapsulation approaches for poorly water soluble drug nanoparticles\" and paper \"highly stable and conductive microcapsules for enhancement of joule heating performance\"?", "answer": "Ulrike Wais"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Who penned both the papers \"the effect of conformation method and sintering technique on the densification and grain growth of nanocrystalline 8 mol yttria stabilized zirconia\" and \"atom probe analysis and magnetic properties of nanocrystalline fe84 3si4b8p3cu0 7\"?", "answer": "Shahriar Jafari"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"effect of an oxygen gradient on the ba2ycu3ox superconductor\" and paper \"a versatile metallo organic spin on process for superconducting thin films\"?", "answer": "P.K. Gallagher"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Who has the highest number of collaborations with the author Swagatika Mohanty?", "answer": "Debadhyan Behera"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "Who has the highest number of collaborations with the author Rebecca H. Brown?", "answer": "Timothy Edward Long"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Who has the highest number of collaborations with the author J. Nunes?", "answer": "Ana P. Piedade"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "With whom does W.-Q. Li collaborate the most frequently?", "answer": "P. K. Bhattacharya"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Yong Huang? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Jinming Chen"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Yumei Zhang? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Huaping Wang"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "With whom does R. June collaborate the most frequently?", "answer": "D. Fyhrie"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "With whom does Subhendu K. Panda collaborate the most frequently?", "answer": "Subhadra Chaudhuri"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "With whom does Javad Berenjian collaborate the most frequently?", "answer": "Hessam AzariJafari"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the individual who collaborates most often with author Paolo Russo?", "answer": "U. Bernini"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators for author V. G. Kharchuk in 2004", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "What is the count of collaborators that author Hans-Peter Rust worked with in 2010", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "How many collaborators does author Rene van Roij have in 2007", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "What is the count of collaborators that author V. Y. Butko worked with in 2018", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators for author Sunil Sharma in 2012", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "What number of people did Tim Durrant collaborate with in the year 2011", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "In 2018, how many individuals collaborated with author Yanhao Yang", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators for author Li Zhao in 2015", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "What is the count of collaborators that author William Walden-Newman worked with in 2011", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "How many collaborators does author K.Y. He have in 1994", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many joint publications do Ashley Buss and R. Christopher Williams have?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "How many papers did Josette Rivory and G. Vuye write together?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "What count of papers have Mei Huang and Robert G. Hill jointly written?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "What count of papers have Sylvie Demouchy and Alexandre Mussi jointly written?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "What count of papers have K. Remack and K. Boku jointly written?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "What count of papers have Aaron C. Hryciw and Michael D. McGehee jointly written?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers written collaboratively by Ki Min Jung and Young Jun Kim?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers written collaboratively by Jiahua He and Yanqiang Qiao?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "How many joint publications do Shuxian Shi and Xiaonong Chen have?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "What is the total number of papers Ji Young Yoon and Won Seok Lyoo co-authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers that cite \"granular l10 fept 0 0 1 thin films for heat assisted magnetic recording\"?", "answer": "32"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "How many scholarly articles have cited the paper \"effect of some admixtures on the setting time and strength evolution of cement pastes at early ages\"?", "answer": "21"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "How many scholarly articles have cited the paper \"al v graphite interface reactions an xafs study of the reactions in a composite interface system\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers that cite \"size effects in submicron exchange bias square elements\"?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference the paper \"processing map for hot working characteristics of a wrought 2205 duplex stainless steel\"?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference the paper \"influence of the interaction strength between supramolecular complexes on the topography of neutral polymer multilayer films\"?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers that cite \"preparation and properties of a new coating method for preparing conductive polyester fibers with permanent conductivity\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "How many scholarly articles have cited the paper \"effects of particle size polishing pad and contact pressure in free abrasive polishing\"?", "answer": "26"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference the paper \"thermal mechanical physical and transport properties of blends of novel oligomer and thermoplastic polysulfone\"?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers that cite \"fermi edge singularity in degenerate n type bulk inas\"?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that \"chirp structure measurement of a supercontinuum pulse based on transient lens effect in tellurite glass\" refers to?", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that \"extraordinary surface plasmon coupled emission using core shell gold nanorods\" refers to?", "answer": "18"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that \"simple system for optical short pulse generation in both active mode locking and self seeding schemes\" refers to?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "What is the count of papers that the paper \"single step laser plasmonic coloration of metal films\" cites?", "answer": "23"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "How many references are there in the \"boron nitride nanotubes and primary human osteoblasts in vitro compatibility and biological interactions under low frequency ultrasound stimulation\" paper?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "How many papers does paper \"crystallization behavior of nd fe b based alloys\" cite?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "What is the number of papers quoted in the paper \"preparation and raman study of b doped si microcrystals\"?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "How many references are there in the \"network array of zinc oxide whiskers\" paper?", "answer": "22"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "How many references are there in the \"a quantitative study of the hardness of a superhard nanocrystalline titanium nitride silicon nitride coating\" paper?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "How many references are there in the \"well aligned multi walled carbon nanotubes emitting natural white light under microwave irradiation\" paper?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "What is the most referenced paper written by Hongmei Zhao?", "answer": "characterization of azo and ag based films prepared by rf magnetron sputtering"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Mitsuki Nakata?", "answer": "vertically aligned ge nanowires on flexible plastic films synthesized by 111 oriented ge seeded vapor liquid solid growth"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author G. Binitha?", "answer": "electrospun \u03b1 fe2o3 nanostructures for supercapacitor applications"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "Can you name the paper by Joshua T. O\u2019Neal that has been cited the most?", "answer": "qcm d investigation of swelling behavior of layer by layer thin films upon exposure to monovalent ions"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "Can you name the paper by Xiaodong Wang that has been cited the most?", "answer": "batio3 tio2 heterostructure nanotube arrays for improved photoelectrochemical and photocatalytic activity"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "What is the most referenced paper written by Philip Adu?", "answer": "surface tunable electrically conductive and inexpensive graphene platelets and their hydrophilic polymer nanocomposites"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "What is the most referenced paper written by A. Otto?", "answer": "raman scattering by bulk phonons in microcrystalline silver and copper via electronic surface excitations"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "Can you name the paper by S. Yang that has been cited the most?", "answer": "on the fracture of solids characterized by one or two parameters theory and practice"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "Can you name the paper by K. Marvin Schulz that has been cited the most?", "answer": "emission enhancement in dielectric nanocomposites"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "Can you name the paper by Jiri Nohava that has been cited the most?", "answer": "a simple basis for determination of the modulus and hydraulic conductivity of human ocular surface using nano indentation"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "What is the number of papers written by the author H. Khassaf?", "answer": "15"}
{"qid": "101", "question": "How many papers did author Byung-se So write?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "Can you tell me the total count of papers that M. Rizwan has written?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "103", "question": "What is the number of papers written by the author Amaresh Das?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "How many papers did author Mitsuhiro Wada write?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "105", "question": "Can you tell me the total count of papers that Abdus Salam Sarkar has written?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "How many works has author J. W. Hustoft contributed to in the form of papers?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "107", "question": "What is the number of papers written by the author Pawel Kamasa?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "108", "question": "Can you tell me the total count of papers that Xiaohan Zhang has written?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "109", "question": "What is the number of papers written by the author D.M. Sidorenko?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "At which location have Jianguo Li and Jinshan Li most frequently collaborated?", "answer": "journal of materials processing technology"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "What was the key venue for collaboration between Matthew Fellew and Geoff Henry?", "answer": "optics letters"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "Where did H. Yoshida and Hisamitsu Endoh primarily collaborate?", "answer": "philosophical magazine"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "What was the key venue for collaboration between M. Radwan and H. S. Abdelmaksoud?", "answer": "journal of materials processing technology"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "Where did Ludwig Bartels and Dominic Martinez-Ta primarily collaborate?", "answer": "scientific reports"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "Which venue did M.P. Drupitha and Golok B. Nando collaborate most?", "answer": "journal of applied polymer science"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "At which location have Nguyen Vu Ly and Jang Myoun Ko most frequently collaborated?", "answer": "electrochimica acta"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "What was the key venue for collaboration between Yongqiang Jiang and Jingdi Zhang?", "answer": "optics letters"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "At which location have Josie Goodall and Aqif Anwar Chaudhry most frequently collaborated?", "answer": "journal of materials chemistry"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "In which venue did Edner Tortella and Ana Costa most often work together?", "answer": "journal of magnetism and magnetic materials"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "To know author C. Leigh Millican, how many people should author Sonia Lucia Fiorilli at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "How many people does author T. Makino need to know at least to know author Man Wang?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "What is the minimum number of individuals author Laizhu Jiang has to be acquainted with to know author Yu Haifeng?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "To know author Elena Del Favero, how many people should author Michela Barattin at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "To know author Ivo Carlos Correa, how many people should author Hongda Cai at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "What is the minimum number of individuals author V.Y. Yakovlev has to be acquainted with to know author V. G. Zorin?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "To know author Donato Belmonte, how many people should author A. Yu. Glamazda at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "What is the minimum number of individuals author Guanjun Hu has to be acquainted with to know author Huang Shuang?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "To know author Liren Xu, how many people should author Thomas Fitzgibbons at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "To know author Libor Kobera, how many people should author P. Brauer at least be acquainted with?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "130", "question": "For a reader of the paper on the mechanism of degradation in si siox ag metal oxide semiconductor solar cells, which paper would you suggest from the list of candidates: effect of processing conditions on superconductive properties of laser deposited ybco thin films, formation of three dimensional nano trees with perpendicular branches by electrodeposition of cusn alloy, solid liquid transition in polydisperse lennard jones systems, comparative study of different silicon oxides used as interfacial passivation layer siny h siox n si in industrial monocrystalline silicon solar cells, band gap structure modification of amorphous anodic al oxide film by ti alloying, high power dual wavelength laser with disordered nd cngg crystals, nonlinear enhancement in photonic crystal slow light waveguides fabricated using cmos compatible process, high drop tube undercooling experiments on tazr alloys, critical behavior of birefringence in the smectic a phase of chiral smectic liquid crystals, size dependence of rotation frequency of individual laser trapped liquid crystal droplets? Kindly respond with the title not the ID.", "answer": "comparative study of different silicon oxides used as interfacial passivation layer siny h siox n si in industrial monocrystalline silicon solar cells"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "Can you recommend a paper for someone who has read a novel ba0 6sr0 4co0 9nb0 1o3 \u03b4 cathode for protonic solid oxide fuel cells from the following options: development of residual stress in sol gel derived pb zr ti o3 films an experimental study, advances in pulsed laser deposition of nitrides and their integration with oxides, segregation of solute atoms in mg ce binary alloy atomic scale novel structures observed by haadf stem, reactive electrode submerged arc process for producing fine non oxide powders, evaluation of ba0 6sr0 4co0 9nb0 1o3 \u03b4 mixed conductor as a cathode for intermediate temperature oxygen ionic solid oxide fuel cells, mechanical deformation study of copper nanowire using atomistic simulation, lithographically defined site selective growth of fe filled multi walled carbon nanotubes using a modified photoresist, creating molecular barriers to acute platelet deposition on damaged arteries with reactive polyethylene glycol, ground states of group iv nanostructures magic structures of diamond and silicon nanocrystals, far infrared study of ferroelectric soft modes by fourier spectroscopy? Please provide the title and not the ID.", "answer": "evaluation of ba0 6sr0 4co0 9nb0 1o3 \u03b4 mixed conductor as a cathode for intermediate temperature oxygen ionic solid oxide fuel cells"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper room temperature single crystal elastic constants of boron carbide? Please select from the candidate list la0 6sr0 4coo3 \u03b4 modified lifepo4 c composite cathodes with improved electrochemical performances, phonon thermal conductivity suppression of bulk silicon nanowire composites for efficient thermoelectric conversion, influence of alternating current ac corona discharge on the superhydrophobicity of sio2 fluorosilicon resin nano composite coating, light induced reactivity of gold and hybrid perovskite as a new possible degradation mechanism in perovskite solar cells, self assembled monolayers of clamped oligo phenylene ethynylene butadiynylene s, polyurethane microcellular elastomers 1 effect of chemical composition on tensile strength and elongation at break of poly ethylene butylene adipate based systems, predicting hardness of covalent ionic solid solution from first principles theory, shock induced localized amorphization in boron carbide, precipitation in two al mg ge alloys, polyacrylate bound tisb2 electrodes for li ion batteries. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "shock induced localized amorphization in boron carbide"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "Can you recommend a paper for someone who has read some physical studies on thexbeo 1 x v2o5 system from the following options: rf magnetron sputtered heteroepitaxial ysz and ceo2 ysz si 001 thin films with improved capacitance voltage characteristics, density functional theory study of bn doped graphene superlattice role of geometrical shape and size, atom resonant squeezed light from a tunable monolithic pprktp parametric amplifier, effect of polymer molecular weight on the structural properties of non aqueous ethyl cellulose gels intended for topical drug delivery, direct determination of x ray reflection phases, piezoelectric materials all solution processed flexible thin film piezoelectric nanogenerator adv mater 45 2012, characterization of magnetic components in the diluted magnetic semiconductor zn 1 x co x o by x ray magnetic circular dichroism, triple raman label encoded gold nanoparticle trimers for simultaneous heavy metal ion detection, temperature dependent leakage current behavior of epitaxial bi0 5na0 5tio3 based thin films made by pulsed laser deposition, in situ monitoring of hydration of magnesium oxysulfate cement paste effect of mgo mgso4 ratio? Please provide the title and not the ID.", "answer": "characterization of magnetic components in the diluted magnetic semiconductor zn 1 x co x o by x ray magnetic circular dichroism"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "If a reader just finished the paper peculiarities of acoustic beam reflection from a fluid solid interface asa meetng abstract, which paper from the listed candidates should they read next: a statistical model of residual strength and fatigue life of composite laminates, room temperature stabilization of nanoscale superionic ag2se, the relationship between cyclic stress strain curve and dislocation structures in cyclically deformed if steel, photo enhanced antibacterial activity of zno graphene quantum dot nanocomposites, preparation and characterization of epoxy \u03b3 aluminum oxide nanocomposites, electrophoretic transport of single stranded dna through a two dimensional nanopore patterned on an in plane heterostructure, acoustic waves at interfaces studied by laser ultrasonics invited, high temperature strength and oxidation behavior of sc3 lu3 co doped \u03b1 sialon, electrochemical synthesis of conical ag2s nanostructures and their optical properties, picosecond spectra of gain switched algaas gaas multiple quantum well lasers? Please provide the paper title, not the ID.", "answer": "acoustic waves at interfaces studied by laser ultrasonics invited"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "If a reader just finished the paper the effect of composition on spinel equilibrium and crystal size in high level waste glass, which paper from the listed candidates should they read next: liquidus temperature composition model for multi component glasses in the fe cr ni and mn spinel primary phase field, electrochemical reduction properties of extended space charge ingap and gap epitaxial layers, converting natural diatomite into nanoporous silicon for eco friendly thermoelectric energy conversion, energy landscape of deformation twinning in bcc and fcc metals, excellent optical thermometry based on single color fluorescence in spherical naeuf 4 phosphor, dual donor zni and vo mediated ferromagnetism in copper doped zno micron scale polycrystalline films a thermally driven defect modulation process, ni doped overlayer hematite nanotube a highly photoactive architecture for utilization of visible light, atomic scale mechanism for pressure induced amorphization of \u03b2 eucryptite, dry type artificial muscles based on pendent sulfonated chitosan and functionalized graphene oxide for greatly enhanced ionic interactions and mechanical stiffness, a crack free anti corrosive coating strategy for magnesium implants under deformation? Please provide the paper title, not the ID.", "answer": "liquidus temperature composition model for multi component glasses in the fe cr ni and mn spinel primary phase field"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "Can you recommend a paper for someone who has read oxidation behavior of hot isostatically pressed silicon nitride containing y2o3 from the following options: dodecagonal quasicrystals in mesoporous silica anew route from hard to soft sphere packings, effects of surface area polymer char oxidation and nio additive on nitridation kinetics of silicon powder compacts, effect of cdcl2 treatment on properties of cdte based solar cells prepared by physical vapor deposition and close spaced sublimation methods, calculated electronic structure of pb1 xmnxte 0 x 11 the role ofland\u03c3valence band maxima, synthesis and luminescent properties of the li0 995 xmgxsi2 xalxn3 eu2 0 005 phosphors, a smart nanoprobe based on fluorescence quenching pegylated nanogels containing gold nanoparticles for monitoring the response to cancer therapy, enhancement of impedance change at low frequency in a thin film magnetoimpedance element, profile evolution for conformal atomic layer deposition over nanotopography, effects of disorder on electronic structures of a si h and a sio2, compact single mode tunable laser using a digital micromirror device? Please provide the title and not the ID.", "answer": "effects of surface area polymer char oxidation and nio additive on nitridation kinetics of silicon powder compacts"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "Can you recommend a paper for someone who has read long range antiferromagnetic order in quasi one dimensional ca 0 83 cuo 2 and sr 0 73 cuo 2 from the following options: preparation and properties of nickel silicide layers by the diffusion and cvd processes using si2cl6 as a source of silicon, transparent yag ceramics by surface softening of nanoparticles in spark plasma sintering, preparation of polymeric janus particles by directional uv induced reactions, use of bacteria to repair cracks in concrete, decay of high frequency phonons in amorphous silicon, homogeneous nucleation of misfit dislocations in strained layers, spray deposited superhydrophobic zno coatings via seed assisted growth, comparing photoelectrochemical methanol oxidation mechanisms for gold versus titanium nitride nanoparticles dispersed in tio2 matrix, flexoelectric effect in the reversal of self polarization and associated changes in the electronic functional properties of bifeo3 thin films, magnetically induced ferroelectricity in bi2cuo4? Please provide the title and not the ID.", "answer": "magnetically induced ferroelectricity in bi2cuo4"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper correction interplay between ferroelastic and metal insulator phase transitions? Please select from the candidate list a novel route combined precursor hydrothermal pretreatment with microwave heating for preparing holey g c3n4 nanosheets with high crystalline quality and extended visible light absorption, effect of morphology on field emission properties of carbon nanocoils and carbon nanotubes, single electron tunneling through molecular quantum dots in a metal insulator semiconductor structure, near field imaging of mid infrared surface phonon polariton propagation, cathodoluminescence investigation of residual stress in er3 yalo3 thin films grown on 110 srtio3 substrate by metal organic chemical vapor deposition, activation and thermal stability of ultra shallow b implants in ge, sulfenic acid doped mesocellular carbon foam as powerful catalyst for activation of v ii v iii reaction in vanadium redox flow battery, a novel thermoplastic sizing containing graphene oxide functionalized with structural analogs of matrix for improving interfacial adhesion of cf pes composites, ferroelasticity in mixed conducting lacoo3 based perovskites a ferroelastic phase transition, mechanical relaxation to rejuvenation transition in a zr based bulk metallic glass. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "ferroelasticity in mixed conducting lacoo3 based perovskites a ferroelastic phase transition"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "For a reader of the paper lattice strain relaxation study in the ga1 xalxsb gasb system by high resolution x ray diffraction, which paper would you suggest from the list of candidates: luminescent properties of nanostructured dy3 and tm3 doped lanthanum chloride prepared by reactive atmosphere processing of sol gel derived lanthanum hydroxide, optimized leaky mode spectroscopy with a single planar film, tunneling anisotropic magnetoresistance driven by magnetic phase transition, microstructure and mechanical properties of epoxy hybrid nanocomposites modified with acrylic tri block copolymer and layered silicate nanoclay, mechanical and corrosion resistance performance of electrodeposited titania nickel nanocomposite coatings, influence of as incorporation on the deviation from vegard s law in the alxga1 xsb gasb system, probing the dielectric environment surrounding poly n isopropylacrylamide in aqueous solution with covalently attached spirobenzopyran, hrtem analysis of the high temperature phases of the newly developed high temperature ni base superalloy vdm 780 premium, water sorption and solubility of methacrylate resin based root canal sealers, determination of the glass transition temperature of poly styrene co divinylbenzene by inverse gas chromatography? Kindly respond with the title not the ID.", "answer": "influence of as incorporation on the deviation from vegard s law in the alxga1 xsb gasb system"}
